Guide to the Everett Needham Case papers A1015
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- TL, unsigned. Young Owen D. To: Sidney Hillman., 1940 July 10 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1940 September 6 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1940 October 10 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1940 October 12 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1940 October 12 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1940 October 15 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1940 October 21 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1942 January 20 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1942 February 17 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1942 April 29 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1942 May 21 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1942 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1942 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1942 October 22 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1943 January 5 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Ada L. Comstock., 1943 May 27 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1943 June 11 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Josephine Case., 1943 August 20 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Young, Owen D. To: Walter Lippman., 1943 August 26 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1943 September 13 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Dexter Teed., 1943 September 14 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1943 September 14 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1943 September 15 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1943 October 27 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- TL, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1943 October 28 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1944 February 9 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1944 September 20 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- TN, signed. Young, Owen D. To: Everett N. Case., 1944 September 21 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Owen D. Young., 1944 December 4 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Telegram. Case, Everett N. To: Deane W. Malott., undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Evan Randolf., 1941 January 15 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1941 February 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Will D. Howe., 1941 February 4 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Hard., 1941 February 11 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1941 March 6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Hofer., 1941 March 10 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1941 March 18 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Neilson Abeel., 1941 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Judd Feickert., 1941 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James W. Moore., 1941 April 5 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1941 April 10 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Richard Young., 1941 April 21 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1941 April 22 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: E.C. Douglas., 1941 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1941 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1941 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Albert Sauveur., 1941 June 17 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Caroline Philips Smith., 1941 June 17 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles J. Young., 1941 June 17 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1941 July 8 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1941 July 8 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John W. Elwood., 1941 December 13 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Harrison., 1941 December 13 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John D. Gorden., 1941 December 22 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Morrill., 1941 December 22 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas Gairy., 1941 October 23 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Deane W. Malott., 1941 October 24 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: W.W. Trench., 1943 January 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter Jessup., 1943 January 18 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Wendell Willkie., 1943 January 18 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson, Jr., 1943 January 18 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Joseph C. Grew., 1943 January 18 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Harry H. Pond., 1943 February 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1943 February 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Eleanor Brereton., 1943 February 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Pulling., 1943 February 3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Wendell Willkie., 1943 February 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mary Hinckley Dearing., 1943 February 10 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Paul J. Sachs., 1942 February 17 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George E. Bates., 1943 February 24 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Commander, Fort Lee., 1943 March 15 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald J. Hall., 1943 March 17 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1943 March 17 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Stuart M. Crocker., 1943 March 18 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Richard Gurney., 1943 March 18 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H. Hamilton Hackney., 1943 March 25 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter, Jr., 1943 March 27 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles J. Young., 1943 April 14 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Young., 1943 April 15 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1943 April 27 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1943 April 28 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde III., 1943 May 12 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James W. Gerard., 1943 May 12 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1943 May 31 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David Robinson., 1943 June 12 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1943 June 14 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Ada Malott., 1943 July 1 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert C. Roberts., 1943 July 16 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Ed Pulling., 1943 July 17 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fremont C. Pect., 1943 July 17 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fremont C. Peck., 1943 August 13 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Langbourne Williams, Jr., 1943 August 24 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Chapman, Jr., 1943 September 1 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- TL, signed. Young, John P. To: Everett & Josephine Case., 1943 September 2 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.M. Beiermeister., 1943 September 3 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Graydon W. Yaple., 1943 September 21 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Chapman, Jr., 1943 September 21 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Stuart Crocker., 1943 September 22 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Case, Everett N. American Palestine Comm. Materials., undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Carl Baum., 1943 September 28 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fremont C. Peck., 1943 September 28 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Pulling., 1943 October 1 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To; Burnham Carter., 1943 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Gen. F.B. Wilby., 1943 October 7 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Graydon W. Yaple., 1943 October 11 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1943 October 13 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1943 October 16 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- TN, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1943 October 25 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1943 October 25 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Copeland Robinson, Jr., 1943 October 26 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Flexner., 1943 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Chalfant Robinson., 1943 October 28 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Randolph Burgess., 1943 November 9 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Swartz., 1943 November 22 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Bernays., 1943 November 23 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Virginia Brown., 1943 November 23 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: T.S. Matthews., 1943 November 24 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.R. de la Torre Bueno, Jr., 1943 December 2 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Stuart Crocker., 1943 December 3 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.E. Kingsley., 1943 December 6 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Victor Hanson., 1943 December 7 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Vantine., 1943 December 8 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Pulling., 1943 December 9 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George D. Stoddard., 1943 December 27 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Samuel Miller., 1945 January 3 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1945 January 4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Bruce Bigelow., 1945 January 5 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Herman P. Thomas., 1945 January 15 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fred Bate., 1945 January 15 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Richard Young., 1945 January 16 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Raymond Rubicam., 1945 January 16 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Stevenson., 1945 January 22 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Avirett., 1945 January 29 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Raymond Rubicam., 1945 January 30 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.B. Boocock., 1945 February 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Carrie Harrad., 1945 February 27 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1945 March 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1945 March 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Niles Trammell., 1945 March 16 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Milton Potter., 1945 March 20 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1945 April 23 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Samuel B. Irwin., 1945 May 7 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Joseph Hunter., 1945 May 24 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.P.G. Fuller., 1945 May 29 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Weeks., 1945 May 29 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David Young., 1945 June 6 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Young., 1945 June 6 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frieda Shipley., 1945 June 18 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson, Jr., 1945 May 18 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. F.A. Foord., 1945 July 9 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Moorhead Kennedy., 1945 July 31 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David Young., 1945 July 31 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: F. Rhea Dulles., 1945 August 4 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Moorhead Kennedy., 1945 August 13 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Ward Madison., 1945 September 12 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde., 1945 September 26 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: G. Dewey Hynes., 1945 October 30 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Daniel Kirby., 1945 November 21 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Capt. C. L. Spencer., 1945 November 22 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas Carroll., 1945 November 23 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Haden G. Fuller., 1945 November 27 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Young., 1945 December 18 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fred Everett., 1945 December 18 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Young., 1945 December 22 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: T.S. Matthews., 1945 December 24 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Raymond Ehrmann., 1945 December 26 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Webster Todd., 1954 January 22 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Richard B. Scandrett, Jr., 1954 January 23 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Clarence Faust., 1954 February 25 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Myers., 1954 March 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Levering Tyson., 1954 March 22 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hines Baker., 1954 March 24 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Stanton., 1954 April 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: W.P. Tolley., 1954 April 12 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Webster Todd., 1954 May 17 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1954 June 4 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C. Dickerman Williams, 1954 July 27 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter Teagle., 1954 July 30 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Irving Wright., 1954 December 29 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Arthur Adams., 1955 January 14 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Langbourne Williams., 1955 May 23 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Jean Comilia., 1955 June 20 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Laurence Rockefeller., 1955 September 18 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Sir Arthur Goodhart., 1955 November 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Abrams., 1955 November 11 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Russell Leffingwell., 1955 November 13 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Abrams., 1955 November 26 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Gertrude Edgarton., 1955 December 20 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Godman., 1956 January 12 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Harold Halm., 1956 January 23 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Telegram. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1956 February 27 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.H. Edmonds., 1956 April 4 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Laurence Rockefeller., 1956 April 16 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Michael Lubbock., 1956 April 19 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Howard Edmonds., 1956 May 7 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Donald Hall., 1956 May 15 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Sally Nichols., 1956 June 6 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Larry MacKenzie., 1956 August 22 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: A. Glen Acheson., 1956 October 5 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Irma & Alan Stevenson., 1956 October 9 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Herbert Brownall, Jr., 1956 October 11 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Larry MacKenzie., 1956 October 23 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank W. Abrams., 1956 December 1 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Samuel Fuller., 1957 January 4 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Edwards., 1957 January 15 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Kurt Sperrhake., 1957 January 15 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Peach., 1957 February 4 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: B.A. Van Houten, 1957 February 6 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Livingston Merchant., 1957 March 29 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Laurence Rockefeller., 1957 May 3 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1957 May 14 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Chester Lang., 1957 May 14 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Namone Balfour., 1957 May 17 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Samuel Fuller., 1957 June 21 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Ramsey, Jr., 1957 June 24 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Leonard Matteson., 1957 December 21 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John W. Elwood., 1942 January 20 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip D. Reed., 1942 January 21 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1942 January 29 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David Pulling., 1942 January 30 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John S. Bryan., 1942 February 9 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Gertrude Chandler., 1942 February 10 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Harrison., 1942 February 17 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip D. Reed., 1942 February 17 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Harold W. Dodds., 1942 February 18 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Allen Hinkle., 1942 February 19 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Nicholas Kelly., 1942 March 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Joseph Quattrone., 1942 March 3 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Woodruff., 1942 March 4 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Allen Hinkel., 1942 March 14 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.E. Love., 1942 April 2 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James C. Colgate., 1942 March 17 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward H. Hume., 1942 April 7 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Ward N. Madison., 1942 April 8 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Aldwyth C. Jones., 1942 April 13 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.P.G. Fuller., 1942 April 31 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Richard Gummers., 1942 April 30 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Earle Balch., 1942 April 30 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank E. Brimmer., 1942 May 2 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frank Houston., 1942 May 4 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Baker., 1942 May 5 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Allan Nevins., 1942 May 5 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Harold G. Murphy., 1942 May 5 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Conyngham., 1942 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H. Copland Robinson., 1942 May 15 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: S.M. Crocker., 1942 May 20 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Paul V. McNutt., 1942 May 26 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Jane Randolph., 1942 May 27 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1942 May 27 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1942 May 27 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David McCord., 1942 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Baker., 1942 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Irving Ives., 1942 June 3 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Harrison., 1942 June 23 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: R. Keith Kane., 1942 June 23 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. Romeike Press Clippings., 1942 June 23 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fred Bate., 1942 June 24 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Wallace B. Donham., 1942 June 29 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Clone., 1942 July 1 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1942 August 25 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Melvin Copeland., 1942 September 19 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Julia Hull., 1942 October 8 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Fred Bate., 1942 October 8 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Myles Mace., 1942 October 13 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dale Warren., 1942 October 23 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Paul Hollister., 1942 October 23 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Pulling., 1942 November 13 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: W.W. Trench., 1942 November 16 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Zechariah Chafee, Jr., 1942 December 1 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas Carroll., 1942 December 9 (Box 11, Folder 53)